SERGIO RUIZ FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER serginator@gmall.com http://www.serginator.com

FullStack JavaScript developer with 7* years industry experience, since the age of 6 with computers and since the age of 12 dealing with code, with strong skills in code quality, performance and continuous integration. Capacity to learn new languages and adaptability on ewe environments in no time thanks to his overall knowledge of languages and operative systems.

WEB DEVELOPMENT HTMLS CSS3 LESS JAVASCRIPT REST AJAX GRUNT, IS

JAVASCRIPT JQUERY ANGULARIS VUE,IS REACTIS WEBCOMPONENTS NODE,IS ZEPTO,IS UNDERSCORE LODASH

CI JENKINS SONAR GRUNT, IS WEBPACK NPM UNIX DOCKER
DATABASES MYSQL SQLITE NOSQL MONGOOB

SCM GIT GITHUB SVN TFS

SECURITY NMAP NETCAT WIRESHARK ETTERCAP MSF NESSUS OPENVAS AIRCRACK-NG NIKTO

DESIGN PHOTOSHOP ZBRUSH SOFTIMAGE | XSI TERRAGEN GIMP 2 INKSCAPE

■ EMPLOYMENT

Programmer Analyst, AURIGAE

Systems Integration Consultant - Programmer, Madrid 2012-01 – 2012-12 CIBER

Programmer at System Integration, I've been developing a social network, Android apps, rest services at BBVA GAE project, sites with Google Sites for Internal documentation at BBVA and Telepitzas's mobile app.

HIM HIM SCS SCS Inactions BB EGG Android SCS In Computer Size 4.40 MST Dec. 2015.

Systems Integration Consultant - Junior Programmer, Madrid 2011-06 - 2012-01

★ PROJECTS

Creator, JS Test

Developer, Movistar TV - Hybrid

2017-01 - Present

Developer, Movistar TV - Hybrid

2015-01 - Present

Developer, Movistar TV -

Movistar TV web application, which allows to watch Live TV and VOD content, and handle your subscriptions, view the EPG and more. Joined the team for one month to speed development of new features.

Main developer, Movistar TV - Chromecast

received:

Chromocust Beceiver for the mobile applications of Movistar TV, which handles to play Live TV and V0D on Chromocust
Eveloped in Angular JS. Also installed and configured all the continuous integration environment with jenkins and Sonar,
and made the Curul; tasks to automate everything, from limiting or testing to opening pull requests automagically
integrating Condon with new translations from the OBs.

Main developer, CSB - Cloud Service

CSB is a panel to manage users, assign resources or services, handle your account as a user... It uses Parallels (POA and PBA). Development of an APS 1.2 to integrate McAfee Multi Access in CSB, front-end (in Dojo Toolkit) and back-end (in Modejs, if for O2 (UK and GER) and WVO (Brazil), Aso made all the ci environment.

Developer, FeedApp

2012-12 — 2013-12

Developer, Movistar TV -

Hybrid Development of the Ui of a set-top box (STB) with satellitericable and internet connection for TNApps and VOD, using SNG and jawaStorpt to communicate with the middlewave. Not I've installed and configured all the continuous integration environment with perish and Scoura, and made the Crusty is stot automate everything, from limiting or testing to opening all requests automage(stay) integrating Crowdin with new translations from the OBs.

supported plan prisons ANY SV Uses insinter Source Impa RNA OF Cold Vision spents challed value great the Cale Vision SV Uses in SNAS Cold Vision SV Uses in SNAS Cold Vision SV Uses SNAS COLD VISION SV USE SNAS COLD

Developer, Telepizza - Mobile app

Developer, BBVA - Google App Engine (GAE)

Development of services and apps for BBVA using Google App Engine (GAB). After the development of several REST services, I created some documentation webs for internal projects using Google Sites and developing gadgets in Google Apps Script.

Main developer, HEEL - Android

Development of a tablet application (Android) for a pharmaceutical laboratory. This app is used to let pharmacists to fill and sign contracts of sale and purchase, with a pharmacy database. It captures the form as a digital image and stores the filled form in CVS format to post-process it.

Developer, TUYYOU - Development of a Social

Social network development using ELGG and modifying it's core. It was running for several years, being announced in several media around the country.

EDUCATION

Web Development with React JS, Imagina

2017-05 — 2017-06

React JS course

Design and conceptualization of videogames, Imagina

5014-11 – 2014-12

Course about design and conceptualization of videogames, It was about rewards, personalities, feedback, homo fabor va homoloders, monorations, casual players vs hardone polyers, Ok localization, equilibrium, interactive design.

Web development with Node.js, Imagina

eworks course using some frameworks like Base, Bootstrap and Foundation.

Web development with Angular JS, Imagina Formación

2015-12 -- 2016-02

An Introduction to Interactive Programming in Python Rice 2013-01

Software development for Android devices Universidad Nacional de Educación a

Distancia - UNED Dreamweaver CS4, Universidad Complutense de Madrid Course certified by UCM about HTML4, CSS2 and Dreamweaver. Engineering in Computer Science, Universidad Complutense de Madrid - UCM Studied Engineering in Computer Science until 3rd grade, passed all programming practices. < AFFILIATION Co-Organizer and member, MadridJS

Meetup

Co-Organizer of MadridJS, helping with talks and organization but with the lack of time, just member since 2015 2011-08 — Present Member, JavaScript study group
Study group formed by several members of the JavaScript community in Madrid to learn and debate about JavaScript
compstem. * EXTRACURRICULAR Codemotion ES 2012, Event plenty of conferences about development. More info here Spain/S 2012, Event plenty of conferences about JavaScript. More info here $Spain/S~2013, \ Event plenty of conferences about JavaScript. \ More info <ahref="http://lanyrd.com/2013/spainjs/">here$ XP Week 2013, Workshops about XP, TDD, Clean Code, Cl, Grunt... I made some slides to talk what 18.#39,ve learnt to my colleages at Telefonica I+D. DEVCON 2013, Development conference for Telefonica TEFCON 2015, Development conferences for Telefonica I+D Madrid 2015-05 SmashingConf Barcelona 2015, Event plenty of conferences about JavaScript, CSS and Design. More info -a href="http://lanyrd.com/2015/smashingconf-barcelona/">here and -a href="http://smashingconf.com/barcelona-2015/">here. |SDayES 2016, Development conference about Madrid 2016-04 JavaScript FrontFest 2017, Development conference about FrontEnd *|SDayES 2017,* Development conference about JavaScript Madrid 2017-05 FrontFest 2018, Development conference about FrontEnd Madrid 2018-02 SPEAKING Game development in JavaScript, MadridJS

It was a conference Carlos and I did about Game Development in JavaScript. It was in CAMON, with around 90 attendees. Here is the video, slides and info about the session.

Workshop: Game programming in JavaScript, 2013

Advanced workshop on how to develop a game without libraries, plain JavaScript, for the GameMe5 event. In this workshop we showed and explained in four hours, step by step, a shootem up demo. The game can be played here and the repowth more info can be watched here.